Here.
Hurry.
Time is money.
Just say it.
We visited the market,
found the shop,
and appraised the goods.
We just need a translator to bargain.
The boss only understands Hokkien.
A translator is 28 yuan per hour,
with a minimum of three hours.
Good deal, right?
Then I should thank you, Miss Li.
You're welcome, Mr. Zhang.
Hurry.
I'm sorry
for making you come all the way here.
Is 'I'm sorry' your catchphrase?
Watch your mouth.
It's okay, she's just like that.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Being able to say whatever you want
is a good thing.
It really is a catchphrase.
Boss.
How much is this?
This is three yuan.
Three.
Let me carry that for you.
Carrying it yourself
is not very convenient.
It's okay.
It's not heavy.
Besides, I'm used to it.
Thank you so much today.
I couldn't find the place alone,
and was afraid of buying the wrong things.
Let alone travel agencies,
even local guides wouldn't take such a small order.
Thank you so much today.
I'm sorry.
You're welcome.
I got my tour guide certificate before,
but never led a tour.
This time, I finally experienced it.
It's so beautiful.
We should take more photos later.
No problem.
I'm so satisfied with my makeup today.
It's rare for me to look this good.
Did you notice?
For their whole family,
she's the one carrying all the bags.
It's quite pitiful.
What's the connection there?
Besides, whether others are pitiful or not,
what does it have to do with me?
Do you have any humanity?
Such a big family,
but they sent a young girl out to buy things alone.
It's so unsafe in an unfamiliar place.
I'm sorry.
My boyfriend loves these.
It's rare for him to get time off and walk around with his family,
so he asked me to buy them.
What about you?
Me?
I'm fine with it.
He brought me on his vacation,
which is already troubling him.
That crown from earlier looked quite nice.
That's a Phoenix Crown.
I even looked it up before coming here.
It's the traditional dress of the She girls here.
It's so beautiful.
Since you're here,
why don't you try it on?
No, thanks.
I'll just look.
What if it's free?
Excuse me.
Is it really free?
Fair and square.
This guy is a friend I met while traveling.
I promise it's not only free,
but the results are also amazing.
Hello, I'm makeup artist Tang Yi.
You can choose a look here first.
Go, go, go.
So basically, all day,
you've been running a losing business.
Sister, for us in the service industry,
the most important thing is the customer's experience.
Alright.
Then you keep serving.
I'm leaving.
Stop.
Translation fees start at three hours.
Your work is not done yet.
Sorry.
Does it look a bit weird?
No.
This is called the Phoenix Dress.
It's the traditional clothing of She ethnic girls in Matou.
It suits you very well.
I don't mean the craftsmanship is bad.
It's my own problem.
I don't usually dress up.
It's very beautiful.
It suits you well.
Isn't this a great service spirit?
Since that's the case,
let's provide a one-stop service to the end.
Yes, exactly, come on.
Strike a pose.
Raise your hands.
Not bad, not bad, not bad.
Step forward.
Right, right, right.
Push forward.
A bit to the left.
A bit more to the right.
Blocking the face.
Not blocking.
Right, good.
Go this way, go that way.
Come, right.
Bring it forward.
Let's get a close-up.
Sit down, right, good.
Move back, come.
Not bad, not bad, not bad.
Looks good.
Let's go take some shots over there.
It looks better there.
Let's go.
Yes, look back.
Where's the reflector?
Here.
Closer, yes.
Up, right.
Come look here.
You're quite expressive on camera.
Not your first time, right?
I majored as a flight attendant,
so I learned facial expression management.
Later I met Zinan.
He said it's not safe to fly everywhere,
so he asked me to quit.
Sorry, I digressed.
So you were a flight attendant major.
Does that mean you're not afraid of heights at all?
I've loved being in high places since I was little.
Looking down from the sky,
everything on the ground seems insignificant.
All the bad things and worries
become so, so small.
There's a paragliding base in Jiudu at Shanmei Reservoir.
You can check it out if you're interested.
I know.
I really wanted to go before I came.
I even made an itinerary.
But later,
his parents wanted to come too,
and bringing his brother made it inconvenient.
So you mean
he made you quit your job,
said he'd take you on a trip,
and ended up bringing his whole family.
Focus on taking pictures.
It's fine. Being in a relationship means accommodating each other.
Although he doesn't like me going out to work,
he treats me very well.
He's my fiancé, after all.
Your phone.
Hello?
Have you bought the seafood yet?
You didn't overspend the money I gave you, did you?
I bought it.
There's still over 200 left.
Zinan, I went to a travel...
Alright.
We'll talk when you get back.
Mom, Dad, and my brother are hungry.
We won't wait for you.
Just use the remaining money for your own meal.
Wait.
Do you want to eat together?
Just spend a few dozen on your meal,
and transfer the 200 to me.
We'll pack some food for you after we finish.
This brick is so red.
Idiot.
A traditional red brick house is naturally built with red bricks.
Then I'll go back and take off my makeup.
I'm really sorry about today.
Sorry for the trouble.
Then just come to the front desk to find us later,
and we'll send the photos to you.
It's fine.
I'll get going then.
No, no, no.
Yiyi, this outfit...
It looks nice,
but it doesn't really suit you.
Yiyi.
This outfit looks great on you.
It suits you so well.
It's like it was tailor-made for you.
Yeah.
What are you wearing?
It's too flashy.
It's all a scam.
Let me tell you,
Zinan works hard for his money.
You can't just spend it casually.
They did it for free.
It didn't cost anything.
It's free now,
but what about when you're done?
They'll definitely force you to buy.
Don't you know?
Yiyi.
You look better without makeup.
Come on, let's wash your face.
We shouldn't take advantage of others.
Now you know better than to take advantage.
When you took advantage of the cab fare,
you didn't say that.
Yeah, why didn't you do this earlier?
Thank you for your kindness,
but Yiyi doesn't need this.
She doesn't need it,
but you do.
All right.
Let's go.
It gives me a headache.
Tell me,
what did Lin Yiyi want to say at the end?
It doesn't matter.
You aren't curious?
I don't believe you.
You
are just stubborn.
I asked you to praise her and you wouldn't.
But you did in the end anyway.
So what if I praised her?
The result is the same.
Nice guys finish last.
Wait for me.
Eight-treasure congee.
How much is this?
It's free.
Thank you.
My eight-treasure congee tastes good, right?
But,
what you said just now
was actually pretty cool.
Do you know how to pronounce these two words?
Konjac.
This didn't exist when I was in junior high.
At that time,
milk tea
was still made from powder.
I need a high-paying job
with full benefits
and steady salary increases every six months
so I can buy
my dream house within four years.
God of Wealth,
I pray to you so sincerely every day.
You heard me, right?
Did you?
I'm editing photos.
Which filter looks good?
Not to mention travel agencies for such small orders,
even local guides don't take them.